It was fun.
楽しかったね
it was fun.
楽しかった
I'm thirsty.
喉乾いた
Are you thirsty?
喉乾いた?
There's a cafe in a little while.
もうちょっとでカフェあるんだよ
i wanna go.
行きたい
i wanna go?
行きたい?
Let's go there, have a drink, and take a break.
そこ行って飲み物を飲んでちょっと休憩しよう
What kind of person do you like?
どんな人が好きなの?
kind person.
優しい人
kind person?
優しい人?
Everyone says they are kind people.
優しい人ってみんな言うじゃん
But maybe someone can tell you how they feel.
でも、気持ちを伝えてくれる人かも
When I don't just like her, but think she's cute,
好きとかだけじゃなくて、可愛いと思った時に、
There are people who tell me that I'm cute.
可愛いって言ってくれたりする人がいる
cute.
可愛い
Is this different?
これは違う?
different.
違う
What about me?
俺とかどうなの?
friend.
友達
Am I a friend?
俺友達?
Seriously?
マジで?
Is it okay to be someone I like?
好きな人でもいいの?
Didn't you say you had a boyfriend?
彼氏いるって言ってなかった?
I haven't heard it.
聞いてないんだけど
Are you a friend?
友達か
So does that mean I have no chance?
じゃあ俺には可能性はないってこと?
Even my boyfriend loves it.
彼氏だって大好きなの
How long have you been together?
どのくらい付き合ってんの?
It's been two years already.
もう2年とか
So when we met, you didn't say anything from the beginning.
じゃあ俺と出会った時、最初から何も言ってなかったじゃん
I was wondering if you noticed even if I didn't say anything.
なんか言わなくても気づいてるかなと思って
I wasn't trying to hide it.
隠してる気はなかったよ
You don't notice.
気づかないよ
thank you.
ありがとうございます
The food was delicious.
お飯おいしかったね
It was delicious.
おいしかった
Huge.
でかさ
I had a boyfriend.
彼氏いたんだ
There it was.
いたよ
So does that mean it's impossible for people like me?
じゃあ俺みたいな人は無理ってこと?
It's not that he's not my type, but I love my boyfriend.
タイプじゃないことはないけど、彼氏大好きだから
I see.
そっか
It's seriously so frustrating.
マジなんかすげえもどかしいな
Come here for a moment.
ちょっとこっち来てよ
This way, this way.
こっちこっち
what?
何?
Okay, come here for a second.
いいからちょっと来て
Isn't it a place you can pass through?
通れるところじゃなくない?
You can pass.
通れるよ
It's a back road.
裏道なんだよね
Don't hit your head.
頭ぶつけないでよ
It's quite narrow.
結構狭いね
narrow?
狭い?
Isn't it dangerous?
危なくない?
Are you okay.
大丈夫
Ah, here here.
あ、ここここ
Huge.
でかさ
Yeah.
うん
Seriously, I can't do it?
マジで俺無理なの?
It's serious.
マジじゃん
I've always wanted to do this.
俺ずっとこうしたいと思ってたんだって
No way.
やだ
What do you think?
どうだ?
That's amazing.
すごいよ
I'll wrap it like this.
こんな風に巻くぞ
Look.
見して
Just for today.
今日だけ
Look from the front.
前から見して
amazing.
すごい
Like this?
こんな風に?
Do you hate it that much?
そんなに嫌なの?
It turned out like this
こんな風になってたんだ
Yo.
よ
Isn't it better if my boyfriend doesn't find out?
彼 氏にバレなきゃよくない?
No.
ダメ
It's okay if they don't find out.
バレなきゃいいでしょ
No.
ダメ
why?
なんで?
After all, you don't know that we're meeting today.
だって別に俺ら今日二人で会ってることは知らないでしょ
Okay then.
じゃあいいでしょ
No.
ダメ
Well, it's already like this.
だ ってもうこんな風になってんじゃん
Look at your pants.
パンツとか見てよ
No.
ダメだよ
Show me.
見せろよ
The system is stiff.
仕組み固くなってる
Don't you really want to?
本当はしたいんじゃないの?
It's okay for me too.
もう俺でもいいだろ
Say it.
言って言えよ
why?
なんで?
Why?
なんでよ
I want this to come out.
これ出たいんじゃん
Let's have some sex.
いろいろとエッチしようよ
why?
なんで?
Doesn't it have something to do with your boyfriend?
彼氏とも関係なくない?
No.
ダメ
I did it too.
俺ともやったよ
I want to do it with my boyfriend too.
俺、彼氏ともやりたいんだよ
My pussy is already like this.
もうなってマンコこんな風になってんじゃん
good?
いい?
No.
ダメ
No, I already brought you to the hotel.
いやもうホテル連れてきたよ
I can't stand it.
我慢できない
why?
なんで?
Listen to what I have to say just for today.
今日だけ言うこと聞いてよ
Then I'll do it here.
じゃあここでするよ
Is it okay?
いいの?
why?
なんで?
Or I'll do it here.
それかここでするよ
Decide which one.
どっちで決めて
why?
なんで?
Decide for yourself.
自分で決めて
Should I stay here or at a hotel?
ここでするかホテルでするか
Which one is better?
どっちがいい?
Shall we do it here?
ここでする?
So where should we do it?
じゃあどこでする?
Hotel.
ホテル
Hotel?
ホテル?
Yeah.
うん
So you're going?
じゃあ行くってこと?
Yeah.
うん
Are you going?
行くの?
I'll do it then.
じゃあやるから
Fanna, this way.
ファンナ、こっち
Why do you look like that?
なんでそんな顔してんの?
Should I say I'll go by myself?
自分で行くって言ったらいいの?
Yeah.
うん
So why don't you make it look like you're having fun?
じゃあ楽しそうにしてくれないと
Yeah.
うん
I couldn't see it well earlier, so can I have a look?
さっきよく見えなかったから、見せてもらっていい?
Open your legs and show me.
足開いて見せて
This is the back.
ここは後ろ
Only one leg.
片足だけ
Are you ticklish?
くすぐったいの?
Now show me your butt.
じゃあお尻見せて
Turn around.
後ろ向いて
Are you ticklish?
くすぐったいの?
Really.
ほんま
You can laugh properly.
ちゃんと笑えるじゃん
Rest your elbows and knees here.
ここに肘、膝乗せて
Put it on your knees.
両膝乗せて
It's on my hand.
手にそこついて
It's going to stick to your butt.
お尻につきだすんだよ
You wish it would end quickly, right?
早く終わればいいなと思ってるでしょ?
Hey, Fanna-chan.
ねえ、ファンナちゃん
Look.
ほ ら
tickles.
くすぐったい
It tickles.
くすぐったいな
It feels good here, right?
ここ気持ちいいんでしょ?
See, you've become quiet.
ほら、おとなしくなった
When I touched it, it became quiet.
こう触ったらおとなしくなった
Don't worry about it.
気にならないでね
Look.
見て
Fanna-chan, look.
ファンナちゃん、見て
I've had enough of tea.
お茶の飲みつぱいしちゃった
It tasted sour.
酸っぱいしちゃったね
Are you crazy?
脳にがってんの
Are you feeling it?
感じてる?
Do you have a face?
顔してる?
Let's try our hand at it.
手を出しちゃおう
Lean back.
もたれかかって
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
It feels good, right?
気持ちいいでしょ?
Aren't you quiet?
おとなしくないの?
picky
好き好きな
of?
の?
Hold it like this.
こう やって持って
Hold your feet.
足持って
It's in full view.
丸見えです
It's completely visible.
丸見えね
It feels amazing.
すごい感じてるじゃん
I have to do Peraperu.
ぺるぺるやらないといけない
Aren't our faces this close?
顔はこんなに近くないの?
Does it feel good?
気持ちいいの?
what happened?
どうしたの?
I got a lot of Kana-chan's pussy.
カナちゃんのマンジいっぱいついた
Kana-chan.
カナちゃん
Get rid of your illness for just one day.
一日も病気を下ろしてよ
yeah?
ん?
Do you like Chan-chan?
ちゃんちゃん好きなの?
Yeah.
うん
Do you like it?
好きなの?
I farted.
おならしたな
Is it okay?
いいの?
Are you farting?
おならしい?
Are you glad you came?
きてよかったでしょ?
Let's hang out.
付き合おうよ
terrible.
やばい
why?
なんで?
So, are you traveling?
で、旅してんの?
Shit shit.
くそくそ
it hurts.
痛い
it hurts?
痛 い?
it hurts.
痛い
Shit shit.
くそくそ
interesting.
面白い
Shit shit.
く そくそ
Is it no good?
ダメなの?
So you got it?
じゃあ分かった?
I don't understand.
分かってない
Got it?
分かった?
Then before bed.
じゃあ寝る前になって
Before going to bed.
寝る前になって
I'll sleep.
寝てあげる
Let me lick your ass.
お尻を舐めさせて
Look forward to it.
お楽しみにしてよ
If you're looking forward to hearing about it, I won't be bored.
お楽しみにこと聞いてくれたら、くすむらないからね
yeah?
ん?
It tickled me.
くすぐったよ
No disturbing voices?
邪魔声しない?
I won't disturb you.
邪魔声しないよ
It felt good, right?
気持ちよかったんでしょ?
You feel it.
感じてるじゃん
I feel sorry for you.
かわんじてるじゃん
Are you feeling it?
感じてる?
Hey, I want to fuck you.
ねえ、くさげたい
It tickled me.
くすぐったね
Look, I can feel it.
ほ ら、感じてるじゃん
Speak out loud.
声出して
It tickled me.
くすぐったね
You feel it.
感じてるじゃん
It tickled me.
くすぐったね
Because it's easy to push.
押し付けやすから
It feels good, right?
気持ちいいんでしょ?
I have to be honest.
正直言わないと
Hey, it really tickled me?
ね え、まじでくすぐった?
Do you want to have fun?
楽しみたいの?
Yeah.
うん
It feels good, right?
気持ちいいんでしょ?
Yeah.
うん
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
Here, your hand.
ほら、手を
You're very sensitive.
すごい敏感だね
It's all wet.
びちゃびちゃだよ
Oh no, it's so wet.
やばい、びちゃびちゃ
Wow.
うわあ
Were you sensitive?
敏感だったの?
Yeah.
うん
amazing.
すごい
Amazing astuteness
凄い敏
feeling.
感
Don't you like it?
嫌 だ?
feeling
気持ち
good?
いい?
Stretch your arms over here.
腕 をこっち伸ばして
appear?
見える?